captubes.com 2019-01-20

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect?

We may collect a minimal amount of personal information when you visit our site, place an order, or subscribe to our newsletter. We will NEVER sell or otherwise give away your information to any third parties, unless you request us to for reasons of special promotional offers and the like. When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You have the right to browse our site anonymously, and do not have to fill out such fields if you desire not to. 

#### What may we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one or more of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website
  * To process transactions
  * The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified June 4th, 2017
